Resource-FindingAidTitle-AT Resource.ID.AT.AT
Archivists' Toolkit Migration Tracer
Resource--Title-AT
Bulk, 1960-1970
Resource-Date-Expression-AT
Resource.ID.AT.AT
Archivists' Toolkit Migration Tracer
5.0 Linear feet Resource-ContainerSummary-AT
Resource-Abstract-AT
Resource-Dimensions-AT
Resource-GeneralPhysicalDescription-AT
Resource-MaterialSpecificDetails-AT
Resource-PhysicalFacet-AT
CNames-PrimaryName-AT. CNames-Subordinate1-AT. CNames-Subordiate2-AT. (CNames-Number-AT) (CNames-Qualifier-AT)
FNames-FamilyName-AT, FNames-Prefix-AT, FNames-Qualifier-AT
PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT
Box 1
Folder 1
Item 1
Resource-Accruals-AT
Resource-Accruals-AT
Resource-Appraisal-AT
Resource-Appraisal-AT
Resource-Arrangement-Note
Resource-Arrangement-Note
Resource-Bibliography-AT
Resource-Bibliography-AT
Resource-BibliographyItem-AT
Resource-BiographicalHistorical-AT
Resource-BiographicalHistorical-AT
Resource-ConditionsGoverningAccess-AT
Resource-ConditionsGoverningAccess-AT
Resource--CustodialHistory-AT
Resource--CustodialHistory-AT
Resource-ExistenceLocationCopies-AT
Resource-ExistenceLocationCopies-AT
Resource-ExistenceLocationOriginals-AT
Resource-ExistenceLocationOriginals-AT
Resource-FilePlan-AT
Resource-FilePlan-AT
Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTCHRONLabel-AT
Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTCHRONTitle1-AT
2000 Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTCHRONEventDesc1-AT
2001 Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTCHRONEventDesc2-AT
Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTLISTLabel-AT
Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTLISTTitle-AT
Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTLISTItem1-AT
Resource-GeneralNoteMULTIPARTLISTItem2-AT
Resource-GeneralNote-AT
Resource-GeneralNote-AT
Resource-ImmediateSourceAcquisition
Resource-ImmediateSourceAcquisition
ResourceLabel--BiogHist--Structured--TopLevel
Resource-BiogHist-structured--part5-text
Resource--BioHist-Structured-Top-part2-Chronology
Christmas 1985 Received MASI w/ Columbus SLP
New Years Day 1986 Crashed MASI
Resource-BiogHist-structured-top-part3-listDefined
MASI SLP
2K
Yeti Big Top
2500 K
Intense Spider 29
4500 K
Resource-biogHist-structured-part4-listOrdered
First
Second
Third
Resource--BiogHist-Structured-Top-part1-text
Resource-Index-AT
Resource-Index-AT
Resource-IndexItemValue
Resource-LegalStatus-AT
Resource-LegalStatus-AT
Resource-OtherFindingAids-AT
Resource-OtherFindingAids-AT
Resource-PhysicalCharacteristicsTechnicalRequirements-AT
Resource-PhysicalCharacteristicsTechnicalRequirements-AT
Resource-RelatedArchivalMaterials-AT
Resource-RelatedArchivalMaterials-AT
Resource-ScopeContents-AT
Resource-ScopeContents-AT
Resource-SeparatedMaterials-AT
Resource-SeparatedMaterials-AT
CNames-PrimaryName-AT. CNames-Subordinate1-AT. CNames-Subordiate2-AT. (CNames-Number-AT) (CNames-Qualifier-AT); CNames-PrimaryName-AT. CNames-Subordinate1-AT. CNames-Subordiate2-AT. (CNames-Number-AT) (CNames-Qualifier-AT) -- Archives; FNames-FamilyName-AT, FNames-Prefix-AT, FNames-Qualifier-AT; FNames-FamilyName-AT, FNames-Prefix-AT, FNames-Qualifier-AT -- Archives; PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT; PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT -- Archives; CNames-PrimaryName-AT |z CNames-Subordinate1-AT |x CNames-Subordiate2-AT; Subjects--Function-AT; Subjects--GenreForm--AT; SubjectsUgly |z GenreForm |x AT; Subjects--Geographic Name--AT; Subjects--Occupation--AT; Subjects--Topical Term--AT; SubjectsUgly |z Topical Term |x AT; Subjects--Uniform Title--AT
- Resource-C01-AT, Bulk, 1999-2000; Resource-C01-Date-AT; Resource-C01-ComponentID-AT; 1.0 Cubic feet Resource-C01-ContainerSummary-AT; PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT
  Resource-C01-ScopecontentNoteLabel-AT
  Resource-C01-ScopecontentNoteContent-AT
  Subjects--Topical Term--AT
  - Resource-C02-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C02=Date-AT; Resource-C02-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C02-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Resource-C03-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C03-Date-AT; Resource-C03-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C03-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Resource-C04-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C04-Date-AT; Resource-C04-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C04-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 4)
        - Resource-C05-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C05-Date-AT; Resource-C05-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C05-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 5)
          - Resource-C06-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C06-Date-AT; Resource-C06-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C06-ContainerSummary-AT; CNames-PrimaryName-AT. CNames-Subordinate1-AT. CNames-Subordiate2-AT. (CNames-Number-AT) (CNames-Qualifier-AT); FNames-FamilyName-AT, FNames-Prefix-AT, FNames-Qualifier-AT; PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 6)
            Resource--C06-Bibliography
            Resource--C06--Bibliography--Head
            c06 bibItem2
            c06 bibItem1
            Resource--c06-Index
            Resource--c06-Index--head
            c06-index1
            c06-index2
            Resource--c06--biogHist-structured
            c06--biogHist-part1
            resource-co6-chronology-bioHist-part2
            1895 Event1 Event2
            1995 Event A Event B
            Resource-c06-definedList
            Intense spider 29
            4500
            Yeti big top
            2700
            Madone 5.5
            3000
            Resource-c06-listOrdered
            Masi
            Intense
            Trek
            Resource-c06-BiogHist-EndPart
            CNames-PrimaryName-AT. CNames-Subordinate1-AT. CNames-Subordiate2-AT. (CNames-Number-AT) (CNames-Qualifier-AT) -- Pictorial works; FNames-FamilyName-AT, FNames-Prefix-AT, FNames-Qualifier-AT -- Pictorial works; PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT -- Pictorial works; Subjects--Function-AT; Subjects--GenreForm--AT; Subjects--Geographic Name--AT; Subjects--Occupation--AT; Subjects--Topical Term--AT; Subjects--Uniform Title--AT
            - Resource-C07-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C07-Date-AT; Resource-C07-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C07-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 7)
              - Resouce-C08-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C08-Date-AT; Resource-C08-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C08-ContainerSummary-At (Box 8, Folder 8, Item 8)
                - Resource-C09-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C09-Date-At; Resource-C09-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C09-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 9, Folder 9, Item 9)
                - Resource-C10-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C10-Date-AT; Resource-C10-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C10-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 10, Folder 10, Item 10)
                - Resource-C11-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C11-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C11-ContainerSummary-AT (Box 11, Folder 11, Item 11)
                - Resource-C12-AT, Bulk, 1960-1970; Resource-C12-Date-AT; Resource-C12-ID-AT; 1.0 Linear feet Resource-C12-ContainerSummary-AT; CNames-PrimaryName-AT. CNames-Subordinate1-AT. CNames-Subordiate2-AT. (CNames-Number-AT) (CNames-Qualifier-AT); FNames-FamilyName-AT, FNames-Prefix-AT, FNames-Qualifier-AT; PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT (Box 12, Folder 12, Item 12)
                Resource-c12-Bib
                Resource-c12-Bib-Head
                New bike
                Old bike
                Resource-c12-Index
                Resource-c12-index-note
                Bike 1
                Bike 2
                Bike 3
                Resource-c12-biogHist-noteLabel
                Resource-c12-part1-text
                Resource-c12-chronology-Part 2
                1895 first date
                1995 second date
                Resource-c12-listDefined--Part3
                Yeti
                Bike 4
                Resource-c12-listOrdered--Part4
                Madone
                Resource-c12-BiogHist-end-part 5
                CNames-PrimaryName-AT. CNames-Subordinate1-AT. CNames-Subordiate2-AT. (CNames-Number-AT) (CNames-Qualifier-AT) -- History-Sources; FNames-FamilyName-AT, FNames-Prefix-AT, FNames-Qualifier-AT -- History-Sources; PNames-Primary-AT, PNames-RestOfName-AT, PNames-Prefix-AT, PName-Number-AT, PNames-Suffix-AT, PNames-Title-AT, (PNames-FullerForm-AT), PNames-Dates-AT, PNames-Qualifier-AT -- History-Sources; Subjects--Function-AT; Subjects--GenreForm--AT; Subjects--Geographic Name--AT; Subjects--Occupation--AT; Subjects--Topical Term--AT; Subjects--Uniform Title--AT